<resources>
    <string name="app_name">clicker</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>

    <string name="term">
        <b>Welcome to eduPlay</b> \n\n

            <b><i>(1) Basic</i></b>\n
            <b><i>(2) Account Security</i></b>

            <b><i>(3) Termination</i></b>\n
            <p>As creator of your eduPlay account you have access and control over the eduPlay account and the devices that are used to access the Service.
            To maintain control over the account and to prevent anyone from accessing the account,
            you should maintain control over the devices that are used to access the Service and not reveal the password nor any payment details
            associated with your account to anyone. You are responsible for updating and maintaining the accuracy of the information you
            provide to us relating to your account. You are also responsible for preventing unauthorized access and use of your account
            by any other than you. We can terminate your account or place your account on hold in order to protect you, eduPlay or our partners from
                conducting or attempting to conduct identity theft or other fraudulent activity. \n\n </p>

            <p>The eduPlay is provided to you free-of-charge. You should use the Services for non-commercial purposes only.
                You will be charged under law if you abuse the terms and conditions.\n\n </p>\n
            <p>The Agreements will continue to apply to you until terminated by either you or eduPlay. You may terminate the Agreements at any time.
            The data will be deleted and will not be recovered when you terminated your account. Please be considered before proceed to terminate
                your accounts. </p>
    </string>

    <string name="about">
         <b>Developers</b> \n\n

        My name is Che Hock Beng from Universiti Malaysia Terengganu (UMT). I am the developer of this system. I am studying the programme called
        Bachelor Computer Science (Software Engineering). This system is my Final Year Projects before I am graduated.
    </string>


    <string-array name="visibility">
        <item>Public</item>
        <item>Private</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="timer">
        <item>10 sec</item>
        <item>30 sec</item>
        <item>60 sec</item>
        <item>120 sec</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
